{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550233372832","data":{"timestamp":" 1550233372832"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_152238"," gameId":" a552c444-56a0-464c-888a-aef7cb112c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550233373867","data":{"timestamp":" 1550233373867"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_152238"," gameId":" a552c444-56a0-464c-888a-aef7cb112c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550233377266","data":{"timestamp":" 1550233377266"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_152238"," gameId":" a552c444-56a0-464c-888a-aef7cb112c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550233378319","data":{"timestamp":" 1550233378319"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_152238"," gameId":" a552c444-56a0-464c-888a-aef7cb112c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550233382746","data":{"timestamp":" 1550233382746"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_152238"," gameId":" a552c444-56a0-464c-888a-aef7cb112c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550233383803","data":{"timestamp":" 1550233383803"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_152238"," gameId":" a552c444-56a0-464c-888a-aef7cb112c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550233386645","data":{"timestamp":" 1550233386645"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_152238"," gameId":" a552c444-56a0-464c-888a-aef7cb112c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550233387697","data":{"timestamp":" 1550233387697"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_152238"," gameId":" a552c444-56a0-464c-888a-aef7cb112c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550233391769","data":{"timestamp":" 1550233391769"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_152238"," gameId":" a552c444-56a0-464c-888a-aef7cb112c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550233392816","data":{"timestamp":" 1550233392816"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_152238"," gameId":" a552c444-56a0-464c-888a-aef7cb112c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550233393998","data":{"timestamp":" 1550233393998"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_152238"," gameId":" a552c444-56a0-464c-888a-aef7cb112c0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}